▍2026 辛辛那提 WTA1000 决赛
高芙 6-2 6-4 佩古拉 · 赛后捧杯致辞
Ladies and gentlemen, Coco Gauff.
女士们，先生们，高芙。
Well, this is cool.
呃，这感觉真好。
Where where is she?
她……她在哪儿？
Oh, right here. Sorry.
哦，就在这儿，不好意思。
No, first I want to congratulate Jess.
不，我想先恭喜杰斯。
You know, you're an incredible player,
你真是个了不起的选手，
that goes without saying,
这个不用说，
and always playing you is tough.
每次和你打都很难打。
I think today just was I don't know
我想今天……我也说不好，
if all the balls are going in on my side today,
是不是我今天球都进了，
but I don't like seeing you
但我真不喜欢看到你
on the other side of the court.
站在球网的另一边。
So, but I like playing with you,
不过我喜欢和你打球，
but yeah, I just want to say congratulations.
但，我就想说一句恭喜。
You're incredible person and player
你既是好人，也是好选手，
and congrats to your team.
也恭喜你的团队。
You guys are also incredible people,
你们也都是了不起的人，
one of the best teams on tour.
巡回赛里最好的团队之一。
And yeah, also just like to thank Jess.
我还想谢谢杰斯。
Like she said, when I first came on tour,
就像她说的，刚上巡回赛时，
she was one of the few players
她是少数几个
that was nice to me.
对我很友善的选手之一。
And that's always, no, seriously,
这一直……不，说真的，
that's always stuck a long way with me
一直伴着我，
and my family, and I have so much respect
也伴着家人，我很尊敬你，
for you.
真心的。
So, it's an honor to share the court
能和你同场竞技是种荣幸，
with you once again, and hopefully you
很高兴再交手一次，也希望你
can run it back a couple times.
以后还能再战几回。
Next I would like to thank my team,
接下来我想谢谢我的团队，
Jaci, Gavin, Maria, Kylin, and Fabian,
杰西加文玛丽亚凯琳法比安，
who's in France right now,
法比安现在人在法国，
who has been helping me.
他一直在帮我。
And my family back at home.
还有在家里的家人。
What a difference a year can make.
一年的变化真的很大。
Especially JC was sitting in that box
尤其是 JC，他去年也在场，
and we were not in a good scenario last
那时候我们的状况并不好，
year and we brought on Gavin and,
后来我们请来了加文，
I feel like they're the dynamic duo.
我觉得他俩现在是最强搭档。
So, it's really a great joy to play tennis.
打网球真的是件很快乐的事，
you guys make the sport
是你们让这项运动
so fun for me and I think along
对我来说变得这么有趣，我想
with that that's just helped me become
这也帮我
a better player in person.
成为了场下更好的自己。
So thank you guys for holding it down
谢谢你们一直撑着这一切，
and thank you to my parents back at home,
也谢谢在家的爸爸妈妈，
my brothers, grandparents, all the family
我的兄弟们、祖父母、所有
and friends that have been cheering for me,
一直为我加油的家人朋友，
praying for me.
一直在为我祈祷。
I facetimed them after the right there
赛后我在场边的椅子上
on the bench.
就跟他们视频通话了，
So it was good to see their their faces
能看到他们的脸
and them smile.
看到他们笑，感觉真好。
Usually I just get a good job text, so it
平常只收到「打得不错」，
was nice to get a little bit more than that.
这次能多一点，感觉很好。
And I would like
我还想
to thank God for just bringing me
感谢上帝，是他带我
through this these tough periods.
走过了这些艰难的日子。
Last year was literally in the parking lot like
去年我真的就是在停车场里，
in tears.
哭得一塌糊涂。
So it's it's a big difference what a year
一年真能带来这么大的不同，
can make.
真的。
So I thank him for pulling me through.
所以我谢谢他把我拉了过来。
And I would also like to thank Bob
我还想谢谢鲍勃
and Pam for putting on, you know,
和帕姆，谢谢他们办了
a great tournament
这么一届精彩的赛事，
and and definitely like Jess said,
还有，就像杰斯说的那样，
the Navarros for investing in tennis,
也谢谢纳瓦罗一家投资网球，
especially women's tennis.
尤其是女子网球。
It's so important and this tournament,
这真的很重要，这项赛事，
the investment that they made to our sport.
他们对这项运动的投入，
I think all the players feel the love here.
球员都感受到了这份爱。
It's one of the easiest tournaments.
这是最舒心的赛事之一。
And I always enjoy coming here.
我一直很喜欢来这儿。
And thank you to all the volunteers,
也谢谢所有志愿者，
the ball kids.
谢谢捡球的孩子们。
I don't know, drivers, the valet drivers.
还有司机、代客泊车的师傅。
I've been the last one out of here
我常常是最后一个走的人，
because of the scheduling.
因为赛程安排的关系。
So, thank you to the valet drivers
所以谢谢泊车的师傅们，
for staying up past midnight
熬到过了半夜
to get my car.
还在帮我取车。
Who else am I missing?
我还漏了谁？
the locker room attendees,
更衣室的工作人员，
laundry, everyone
洗衣房的，所有
that makes this tournament possible.
让这届赛事得以举行的人。
It truly feel welcomed here.
在这儿我真的感觉很受欢迎。
Every time I turn a corner, there's a smile,
每次转个弯都能看到笑脸，
a person saying good morning
有人跟我说早上好，
and and it really makes my day.
这真的能让我一整天都开心。
And thank you to you guys, the fans.
也谢谢你们，谢谢球迷们。
Like Jess said, this is a tournament.
就像杰斯说，这是一项赛事，
I think a lot of the players,
我觉得很多选手，
especially us American players,
尤其是我们美国选手，
sign the most because there's
这儿的签名，我们签得最多，
so many heartfelt stories and voices
有太多真挚的故事和声音，
and gifts that you guys have given me.
还有你们送我的礼物。
actually like two times
说实话，这一周
this this week I I like cried
我有两次
in my room just from all the support
一个人在房间里哭了，
that I was getting.
就是因为收到的这些支持。
Just some of the stories
有人跟我讲过一些故事，
that people have been sharing with me how
说的是我赢球或输球，
my tennis win or lose gives them joy.
怎么能给他们带来快乐。
It just makes me so happy to be out here
这让我特别开心能站在这儿，
and fight every moment.
每一分都全力去打。
So thank you guys for supporting me
谢谢你们支持我，
and supporting us
支持我们，
and I hope I didn't forget anything else
希望我没漏掉什么，
but yeah thank you all.
总之，谢谢大家。
And I'll see you guys next year.
明年再见。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Coco, will you stand right here and hold
高芙，能不能站到这儿，
that trophy up?
把奖杯举起来？
Ladies and gentlemen,
女士们，先生们，
may I present to you your 2026 Cincinnati
请允许我介绍你们的 2026
Open Women's Singles Champion,
辛辛那提公开赛女单冠军，
Coco Gauff.
高芙。